There was a customer who made an investment keeping in mind the education and marriage of his children,
where he could get good returns. He started investing ₹10,000 a month.
Due
to the investment, his family got ₹11,000 instead of ₹10. So now his children's
education and marriage will be completed
[Music] and he needed money. He
went to the company and said that he wants his investment money back. The company said no, if we
give it to you in between, we will give less money. You will have to take a loan on your own money and
he had to pay income tax on it. His money has not come tax free.
So what kind of investment should be made where if there is an early death, a large
amount is given to the family and the children's education, marriage or whatever financial
planning is not disturbed. What kind of investment should be made where the money comes tax
free. What kind of investment should be made where the money comes tax free. When the money is invested, you can withdraw it. So
keep all these solutions in mind. I have come for you with only one plan.
Watch this entire video. It will definitely help you in your financial planning. If you
like the video, subscribe to my YouTube channel Anil Rajbhar. Triple Face Do Like Share and Subscribe
And to purchase this plan do call
on 9909403412 Thank you Now I have made this video after working very hard This picture is
a lot of hard work After that I have made this plan where suppose
first you will see in the column the age is written from 20 years to 45 After that
if the customer dies a natural death then how much money will he get This is crore rupees If
the customer dies in an accident as written in the second column then this much
money will be received 2 crore rupees If the accident is because he has gone to watch a government transport
movie or there is a fire there If it happens at any government place
then the customer will get three crores There is an accident near Durga
but the customer does not die but he has become disabled then also he will get one crore rupees If
nothing happens to the customer He survives for a long time then also he
will get 1 crore or more And the money he will get will be tax free I have told you all this in the table
now you Look at an example, look at this table carefully. Suppose
the customer is 30 years old. Here he has to invest Rs. 715
for 12 years. He will get benefits for up to 40 years. How much does he have to invest for 12 years?
At the age of 30, here you will see the amount. He
has to invest Rs. 715 for 12 years. Benefits will continue for 40 years. Now
suppose after taking the policy or making this investment, a few days after that
the customer dies in an accident. How much will he get? Rs. 2 crore.
Suppose he dies due to some disease, heart attack, or anything, even then he will
get Rs. 1 crore. And even if he becomes disabled in an accident, he will get Rs. 1 crore. And
if nothing happens to the customer, then he will get Rs. 7413000 on maturity at the age of 40.
If he gets 10% return, if he gets 8% return, then he will get Rs. 32 lakh. If he gets 15% return, or 12%
return, then he will get around Rs. 1 crore. 56 lakhs and if the market gives 15% return
, then you will get 4 crore 16 lakh rupees and if the market
gives 15% return, I am telling you the returns of this fund, wherever
you invest, it has a return of 23.56%, if the average return of 23% is for 40 years, then it becomes up to 57 crores, this
is the power of equity,
you will get more than the power compound, you lived more and the market gave good returns, the market share
market started in India in 1979, from 100 points, today
it is 62000, the person who invested ₹100 has become 1000, this is 4042 years old, so if
you also have this investment for 40 years, then in this way you can get returns,
even if you get an average of 15%, you are still getting 4 crore rupees tax free, this
money is tax free and the best thing is that if you need money in between,
then you can withdraw, there is no need to take any loan,
this is from Dainik Bhaskar There is a news where it is written that there is ULIP for both Bhima and Niwas,
United Insurance Plan. What I am talking to you about
is that the insurance news that you are getting with ULIP is available under term insurance, like
in Europe, suppose you invest ₹50000 then you
will get 10 times 50 lakh insurance, but here you are getting an insurance cover of ₹1 crore or more, so
you can combine both ULIP and Term Plan,
or you can combine Mutual Fund and Term Plan, or you
can do both SIP and Term Plan, so in this plan, you are getting both these benefits, Plastic
Investment Plan, Town Life Insurance.
Now I meet many customers who
Directly, like I have a young friend, I have a friend of 25 years, he says,
Anil bhai, I have to invest directly, as soon as I
get my salary etc., I prefer to invest. There are many people who
invest in property, some people invest in mutual funds,
invest in the market, invest in gold,
now for example, a customer invests ₹100000 in gold, he has made
a lump sum investment, some small property,
now think if unfortunately he dies early, then
how much money will he get for the lakh rupees that he invested, he will get one and a half lakh,
two lakh, three lakh in one or two years, will he get ₹1 crore, he will never get it,
now whatever they invest, let's say there is tax in property, there is tax in gold,
they come home in lump sum mutual fund and nothing happens to them, they
had to invest for so long, they invested and they got the profit that they were supposed to make and
they got the profit, so what profit They have received it tax free,
if you are in mutual fund then also 10% long term capital
money will come back to you, it will come tax free under section 10 of income tax and sometimes
customer care does it like suppose there is a person whose age is 25 or 30 years,
he has a child of one or two or three years, he said that I want to make such an investment where I
get a good return of around 15%, suppose I invest in mutual fund
in my name or in some other investment and I
will get a good return, then my children's education and marriage will be done easily but unfortunately if
he dies, suppose he was paying premium in a mutual fund SIP,
he dies, even if he had started with 10000, then he will get 12000 instead of 10000,
but now how will the child's education and marriage be completed,
if unfortunately you are not there then also your children's education and marriage or whatever other
financial goal of your family must be completed
now when When it comes to that, there are charges in URI.
As soon as the customer sees the travel, he will say that Anil bhai, there are charges in this
when you take insurance of one crore rupees. But if I tell you,
if you get back double the charge of the charge that you are paying, that suppose you
paid a charge of 5000 rupees but you will get back double of it, i.e. 10000 rupees. If you pay
the premium for 12 years but you get back double the money paid for 40 years, then how will it be? That means
your insurance charge of ₹1 crore is coming back along with the charges
and the investment money is getting invested separately.
So how will it feel if
a 30 year old person purchases this and is making payment for 12 years,
he has kept the benefit of 40 years policy including premium, all the charges etc., GST etc.,
after adding the rider etc., it is 7177 and he
has selected five funds for investment. Here you get 11 funds for investment. The customer I am selecting
a big fund, I have selected the top 200 fund, I
have selected the multi fund and recently, not recently, the emerging opportunity function has been launched, it
is only ₹10, you can definitely buy it separately, so
they have invested in it
, you have got the accidental benefit and the benefit for permanent disabilities
and the premium has been shown to you separately,
₹75 for 12 years. Now let's go, I have told you that you
get back the money you have paid with double the charges. Like, let's go first,
what is your premium location charges, ₹6522, these charges were levied, now see in the 10th year,
₹130044, that means ₹6500 buy ₹6522 exactly double, ₹134
has been added to your phone, now in the second year, what will be your premium charges,
₹3261 and the first year's hefty charges were ₹8220, add both of these. And
if you double these then it becomes 22972. This has been added to your charges in the third year, your premium
from location charges of 27 rupees 17 plus next year's mortality charges of 8417,
after adding both if you double them then it will be 2279. So in this way, whatever your
charges are, see them every year in the complete table,
it gets doubled and says for 40 years and this is getting added to your fine video, so your normal
investment was also being made there and the insurance money which
has been deducted from you is also getting back and you are getting the benefit of ₹1 crore
of insurance. Now, as I had told in the beginning that during the time of Koyal, a lot
of customers needed money who had chosen normal savings plan.
When you went to withdraw the money, the company said that if you stop here,
you will incur a loss and you cannot withdraw the money and if you want to
take a loan, then the loan rate is higher than the rate of this plan which you have
already bought. So this plan gives you the facility of parcel withdrawal. Parcel withdrawal
means that after 5 years, if you need money, then you can withdraw it like this, there
is no need to return it and you do not have to pay any dues. This is a very unique feature,
the benefit of which you must take.
The second benefit of this plan is that you get not just one but 11 funds to invest in.
Now whatever your retirement is in 11 funds, you have to keep high equity,
keep a balanced fund, go to the bone side in safe and save money, you
can also select the fund. Thirdly, in this policy, you get the benefit of switching between funds.
This is a very unique benefit. How does this switching work? I
will try to explain to you. Let us take an example. Before that, the market
was between 55 to 60 thousand, around 2021, if you see, the stock market
crashed and went down to 25000. Now, suppose you
had invested ₹1 lakh in 2021, ₹1 lakh,
but if you had these funds, there is an option of switching or if you
had taken this plan, then what would you do, you take the fund from equity and put it
in the depth side, where the cover is fixed, where the money does
not go down, it is safe for fat friends, so if you directly
switched to the phone without any charger, then suppose you
have put the amount of one lakh rupees only in the other side, where you will get a return of seven to eight percent, so in a year
your money which grew from ₹1 lakh to ₹7000 and not ₹50000, now when
the market has come back to ₹25000, which has increased more than double, now you
take it back from your dark fan and switch it If you are in the equity side, then your Rs. 1 lakh 7000 is
more than double, the market is big, so your money has also become more than ₹ 2 lakh, so where
the customer's Rs. 50 thousand doubled, then if
the market is big, then it is 100% bigger, so your Rs. 50000 became Rs. 75000,
not Rs. 2 lakh and a quarter, you could do de-switching, if this kind of benefit
is available in any of your investments, then you can make a good profit, if the market is falling,
then you do not need to be afraid, you put it in the market, when the market
starts rising, then put it back in the equity side, now your money
will keep growing and the whole money is taxed, so while investing in this, you
are getting benefit in ATC through income tax and whenever you withdraw money, it
will come tax free in 10-10 days, so it is giving you high returns and also giving an opportunity to invest
and also giving high insurance cover. So this is a very good benefit,
everybody should take this plan because to take this plan, like normal, if you
want to have insurance
and you don't need to be a graduate, you can even fail in 5th and you
can take it after 45,
if you are more than 45, then you are required to be 12th pass and even if your income
is not much, even if it is 2-3 lakh rupees, then also you can purchase this plan, the minimum starts from 50 lakh,
after that it depends on your income, so how much can you take,
like a person between 40 to 45
gets 15 to 20 times insurance, he gets 20 * insurance, so in this way,
how much time matches your income, you get insurance for that much,
so here the income criteria is not so much, there is a boundary
criteria of education, you can purchase high semester, a person from 18 years
to 665 can also purchase this policy,
recently in this plan a A new fund has been launched called Emerging Opportunity
Fund
. You can start with a fund of ₹10. You will get very good returns. If
I talk about other funds of this company,
if you look at their returns, for example, the return given here for Multi Fund is
21.05%. At that time, the benchmark, which is Sensex, has given a return of only 12.39%.
In this way, you can try different funds and see how you want to invest.
11 funds and this new fund has come, it is very systematic, starting at ₹10. You
can invest in this as well. Another unique benefit is that if the customer
is 40 years old, he has purchased the policy for 40 years, i.e. the policy is till the age of 10
It will run now for example,
for example,
if we come further of 75 lakhs, now if the customer dies,
you will get the example
, so this is a very good option, where as I told in the beginning that
three more things can happen in a person's life, either the person will live less or more or he
will have some disease or disability, in all the three cases you are getting a good investment and income
option, that too touch free, so to purchase this plan today,
contact Anil Rajpurohit 9909403412